<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="77">
	<author>Mmtrx</author>
	<version>1.2.8.5a</version>
	<title>
		<en>Better Contracts</en>
	</title>
	<description>
		<en>
			<![CDATA[
"Should I take those three fertilizer missions, or rather the 2.3 ha potato harvesting contract?" "How much liquid fertilizer will I need for this job?" If you ever asked yourself questions like these, this mod will help to find the answers.

The maximum number of contracts and the amount generated per cycle is automatically adjusted to the number of fields on the map.
 
You can immediately generate new contracts through the "New Contracts" button, or delete all of them with the "Clear Contracts" button.

You can sort the available contracts by type and field number, by total profit, or by profit per minute, to make it easier to find the one you desire.
 
You can set the allowed maximum number of concurrently avtive contracts.
 
With the "Details" button you can toggle on/ off the display of additional contract information. Like cost estimates for usage material as fertilizer, herbicide, or seeds. For harvest and baling contracts, it shows the minimum amount to be delivered, and the amount that you can keep (and sell). From this it calculates the total profit value for a contract, i.e. reward minus cost for fertilize/ spray/ sow contracts, and reward plus value of kept harvest for harvest/ baling contracts. It even estimates the time you will probably need for total completion of the job, by taking into account the work speed and work width of the appropriate leasing vehicles/ tools that are offered with the contract.

Disclaimer: All values shown in details display are ESTIMATES. You should not take them absolutely, but rather as an indication of what contracts to prefer among others.

The mod keeps track of the amount of contracts you completed for each of the NPC farmers (number of completed jobs is displayed below the farmers image, if "Details" on). If you enable the optional discount mode or hard mode options (on the mods settings page), the amount of completed jobs influence gameplay.

Changelog v1.2.8.5
- Force plow after root crop harvest (#123). Insta-ferment separate setting (#158)
- Save NPC farmland owners to farmland.xml (#153).
- Support chaff mission 

Changelog v1.2.8.0
- Tweak plow reward. Sort per NPC and contract value (#137) 
- Allow mowers/ swathers on harvest missions (#137)
- Allow Göweil mission bales (#144)

Changelog v1.2.7.9
- Allow 240er PackedBales as mission bales, i.e. insta ferment (needs mod arcusin Multipack D14) (#131)
- Add 240er bales to Kuhn sw4014 wrapper 

Changelog v1.2.7.8:
- let player instant-ferment wrapped bales
- allow mission bales in storage
- catch unknown fillTypes
- add "off" values to hardMode settings
- Allow forage wagon on grass missions (#118)
- format reward values > 100.000 (#113)
- read userDefined from modSettings/FS22_BetterContracts/<mapName>/ (issue #115)

Changelog v1.2.7.5:
- add all farms active missions display (MP only)
- increase settings range for harvest success, separate setting for baling
- add 2nd progress bar for active harvest contracts 
- fix Maize+ issue with Pumps'n Hoses BGA 
- add setting to change time interval between contract generation runs
- fix missing icon for roller missions, do not display negative "to go" values
- fix mission visual tags for MP: renderIcon(). 

Changelog v1.2.7.0:
- fix issue mouse click Buy Farmland
- add setting to change harvest contract success factor 
- visual tags for mission fields and vehicles
- show leased vehicles for active contracts 

Changelog v1.2.6.2:
- UI settings page in main menu
- display farmland owner in farmland buy/sell view of ingame menu map
- display number of completed jobs under farmers image (if details on) 

Changelog v1.2.5.0:
- hard mode: active contracts time out at midnght, penalty for cancelling
- discount mode: get discounted field price, based on number of missions
- fewer warnings on missing mission vehicles 

Changelog v1.2.4.4:
- fixed filter buttons to show other mission types, if available
- fixed "time left" display for transport contracts in MP game
- weed, fertilize contracts can now also be configured for lazyNPC
- compatibility with other contract mods

Changelog v1.2.4.2:
- "lazy NPCs" (leave more work for contracts) can be configured on/ off
- maximum number of active contracts configurable 
- indicator for active contracts with borrowed equipment 
- clear / new contracts buttons in MP games only work for master user
- recognize FS22_DynamicMissionVehicles

Changelog v1.2.4.0:
- Added (interim) fix for "lazy NPCs": leave more work for contracts
- Allow for (future) other contract types 
- Fixed screen resolution issues

Changelog v1.2.3.0:
- Added display filter function for contracts list 

Changelog v1.2.2.0:
- Adjusted calculation of keep / deliver values for harvest / baling contracts
- Added conflicts prevention with other mods
- Added support for FS22_SupplyTransportContracts, FS22_TransportMissions
]]>
		</en>
		<de>
			<![CDATA[
"Mach ich jetzt diese drei Düngemissionen, oder doch lieber den 2.3 ha Kartoffelernte-Vertrag?" "Wieviel Flüssigdünger brauche ich für diesen Auftrag?" Falls Sie sich je derartige Fragen gestellt haben, hilft Ihnen dieser Mod bei den Antworten.

Die Maximalzahl sowie die Anzahl der jeweils neu generierten Verträge wird automatisch an die Zahl der Felder auf der Karte angepasst.
 
Sie können über die Schaltfläche "Neue Verträge" sofort neue Verträge generieren oder alle mit dem Button "Liste löschen" entfernen.

Sie können die Vertragsliste sortieren nach Vertragstyp/ Feldnummer, nach Gesamtprofit, und nach Profit pro Minute, um einen gewünschten Vertrag schnell zu finden.
 
Sie können die erlaubte Maximalzahl gleichzeitig aktiver Verträge einstellen.
 
Mit dem "Details" Button kann die Anzeige der zusätzlichen Vertragsdetails ein- und ausgeschaltet werden. Z.B. die geschätzten Kosten des Verbrauchsmaterials (Dünger, Pflanzenschutzmittel, Saatgut). Bei Ernte- und Gras-Missionen wird die abzuliefernde Mindestmenge angezeigt, sowie die Erntemenge, die Sie behalten (und verkaufen) können. Daraus ermittelt der Mod den Gesamtertrag der Mission, also Belohnung minus Kosten für Dünge-, Spritz-, und Sähen-Verträge; und Belohnung plus Wert der behaltenen Erntemenge bei den Ernte- und Gras-Verträgen. Er schätzt sogar die Gesamtzeit, die Sie für die Erledigung des Auftrags benötigen werden, und berücksichtigt dafür Arbeitsgeschwindigkeit und Arbeitsbreite der entsprechenden Leasing-Geräte, die für den Vertrag angeboten werden.

Warnung: Alle in der Detailanzeige angegebenen Werte sind GESCHÄTZT. Sie sollten sie also nicht als absolute Zahlen verstehen, sondern als Hinweis, welche Verträge vielleicht anderen vorzuziehen sind.

Die Mod merkt sich die Anzahl Verträge, die Sie für jeden der NPC Farmer abgeschlossen haben (die Zahl wird unter dem Bild des Farmers angezeigt, wenn "Details" an ist). Wenn der optionale Discount Modus oder der Hard Modus aktiviert wird, beeinflusst die Anzahl abgeschlossener Jobs das Spielgeschehen.

Changelog v1.2.8.5
- Wurzelfrüchte erfordern Pflügen (#123). Schnell-gären als separates Setting (#158)
- NPC Farmland-Besitzer speichern, damit nach Restart ein Feld noch den selben Besitzer hat (#153).
- Unterstützung für Häckselaufträge (FS22_ChaffMissions)

Changelog v1.2.8.0
- Tweak plow reward. Sort per NPC and contract value (#137) 
- Allow mowers/ swathers on harvest missions (#137)
- Allow Göweil mission bales (#144)

Changelog v1.2.7.9
- Gepackte 240er Ballen können mit dem im Mod enthaltenen arcusin Multipack D14 nun auch bei Gras-Missionen verwendet werden (#131)
- Kuhn sw4014 Ballenwickler (im Mod) verarbeitet auch gepackte 240er Ballen 

Changelog v1.2.7.8:
- Spieler kann gewickelte Grasballen schnell-gären (um z.B. stationäre Ballenpressen auch für Silage-Missionen zu nutzen)
- Im Hard Modus können einzelne Settings auf "aus" gestellt werden
- Ladewagen können für Gras-Missionen benutzt werden (#118)
- Vetragswerte > 100.000 werden anders formatiert (#113)
- userDefined.xml wird nun in modSettings/FS22_BetterContracts/<mapName>/ gesucht (#115)

Changelog v1.2.7.5:
- Anzeige aktiver Verträge für alle Farmen (MP)
- Wertebereich für Ernte-Erfog vergrößert, separate Einstellung für Gras-Missionen
- Zweiter Fortschrittsbalken für aktive Ernte-Verträge
- Fix für Maize+ / Pumps'n Hoses BGA
- Einstellung für Zeitintervall: wie häufig sollen neue Verträge erzeugt werden
- Fehlendes Icon für Walzmissionen ergänzt. Keine negativen "to go" Werte anzeigen 
- Missions-Icons bei MP repariert

Changelog v1.2.7.0:
- Fixed: Farmland kaufen mit Mausklick
- neue Einstellung für Erfolgsfaktor bei Ernte-Verträgen
- Icons für Missions-Felder und -Fahrzeuge auf Übersichtskarte
- Anzeige geleaster Fahrzeuge für aktive Verträge

Changelog v1.2.6.2:
- UI Einstellungs-Seite im Hauptmenu
- Anzeige der Farmland-Besitzer im Felder-kaufen/verkaufen Modus der Kartenansicht
- Anzeige der Anzahl abgeschlossener Verträge unter dem Bild des Farmers (wenn Details an) 

Changelog v1.2.5.0:
- Hard mode: Aktive Verträge müssen vor Mitternacht beendet sein, Vertragsstrafe für abgebrochene Verträge
- Discount mode: Feldpreise verringern sich mit der Anzahl erfolgreicher Verträge
- Weniger Warnungen bei fehlenden Vertragsfahrzeugen 

Changelog v1.2.4.4:
- Anzeigefilter-Buttons berücksichtigen nun auch andere Vertragstypen, wenn vorhanden
- Detail-Anzeige der Restlaufzeit von Transportverträgen repariert (Multiplayer-Modus)
- Verträge zum Düngen und Jäten können nun auch per lazyNPC konfiguriert werden
- Kompatibilität mit anderen Vertrags-Mods

Changelog v1.2.4.2:
- "Faule NPCs" (mehr Feldarbeit für Verträge) kann konfiguriert werden
- Maximalzahl gleichzeitig aktiver Verträge kann konfiguriert werden 
- Kennzeichnung aktiver Verträge mit Leihgeräten 
- In Multiplayer-Spielen sind die Buttons "Neue Verträge" und "Liste löschen" nur für Administratoren aktiv
- Mod-Erkennung FS22_DynamicMissionVehicles

Changelog v1.2.4.0:
- Temporärer Fix "Faule NPCs": Mehr (Ernte-)Verträge verfügbar
- Weitere Vertragstypen möglich 
- Probleme mit verschiedenen Bildschirmformaten behoben 

Changelog v1.2.3.0:
- Anzeigefilter für die Vertragsliste hinzugefügt 

Changelog v1.2.2.0:
- Berechnung der Mindestliefer- und Eigenmengen angepasst bei Ernte- und Gras-Verträgen
- Konfliktvermeidung mit anderen Mods
- Unterstützung für FS22_SupplyTransportContracts, FS22_TransportMissions
]]>
		</de>
		<fr>
			<![CDATA[
Ce mod permet d'améliorer le système de contrat, à la fois en solo et multijoueur.
"Devrais-je accepter ces 3 missions de fertilisation ou plutôt la récolte de 2.3 ha de pommes de terre ?" "Combien d'engrais me faudra-t-il pour cette mission et à quel prix ?" Si vous vous posez toutes ces questions, ce mod vous donnera toutes les informations sur les contrats pour y répondre.

Le nombre maximum et la quantité de contrat générés sont désormais automatiquement ajustés au nombre de champs de la carte.
 
Vous pouvez désormais générer de nouveaux contrats via le bouton "Nouveaux contrats" et même effacer ceux que vous n'avez pas activé depuis l'écran de gestion des contrats.

Tri des contrats par type/ champs, bénéfice attendu et profit par minute pour vous permettre de trouver plus facilement celui que vous désirez.

Vous pouvez activer plusieurs contrats à la fois.
 
Affichage des détails supplémentaires des contrats directement à l'aide d'un raccourci clavier depuis le menu des contrats. En plus du type de contrat et du numéro+taille du champ, vous trouverez maintenant les coûts estimés du contrat (engrais, herbicide, semence), le surplus de récolte ou de pressage, le calcul automatique du profit net généré. Il y a même l'affichage du temps que vous passerez à réaliser le contrat avec le matériel proposé en location avec celui-ci.

Avertissement: toutes les valeurs indiquées dans l'affichage détaillé sont des ESTIMATIONS. Il ne faut donc pas les considérer comme des chiffres absolus, mais plutôt comme une indication des contrats qui pourraient être préférés à d'autres.

Le mod se souvient du nombre de contrats que vous avez conclus pour chacun des NPC fermiers (le nombre est affiché sous l'image du fermier lorsque "Détails" est activé). Si le mode discount ou le mode dur est activé, le nombre de jobs terminés influe sur le jeu.

Changelog v1.2.6.2 :
- page des paramètres dans le menu principal
- affichage du propriétaire de la terre agricole dans la vue achat/vente de la carte du menu du jeu
- affichage du nombre de travaux terminés sous l'image des fermiers (si détails) 

Changelog v1.2.5.0 :
- mode difficile : les contrats actifs se terminent à minuit, pénalité pour annulation.
- mode discount : obtention d'une réduction sur le prix du champ, en fonction du nombre de missions
- moins d'avertissements sur les véhicules de mission manquants 

Changelog v1.2.4.4:
- correction des boutons de filtrage pour afficher les autres types de mission, si disponibles
- correction de l'affichage du "temps restant" pour les contrats de transport (Multiplayer jeu)
- les contrats de désherbage et de fertilisation peuvent désormais être configurés pour lazyNPC
- compatibilité avec d'autres mods de contrat

Changelog v1.2.4.2 :
- "NPCs paresseux" (plus de travail pour les contrats) peut être configuré
- Le nombre maximum de contrats actifs en même temps peut être configuré 
- Marquage des contrats actifs avec des appareils de prêt 
- Dans les jeux multi-joueurs, les boutons "Rafraîchir" et "Purger" ne sont actifs que pour les administrateurs.
- Reconnaissance du mod FS22_DynamicMissionVehicles

- Ajout d'un correctif (provisoire) "NPC paresseux": laisser plus de travail aux contrats
- Permettre (à l'avenir) d'autres types de contrats 
- Correction des problèmes de résolution d'écran

Changelog v1.2.3.0:
- Ajout d'une fonction de filtre d'affichage pour la liste des contrats 

Changelog v1.2.2.0:
- Calcul ajusté des valeurs de conservation et de livraison pour les contrats de récolte et de mise en balles
- Ajout de la prévention des conflits avec d'autres mods
- Ajout de support pour FS22_SupplyTransportContracts, FS22_TransportMissions
]]>
		</fr>
		<br>
			<![CDATA[
"Devo aceitar essas três missões de fertilizantes, ou melhor, o contrato de colheita de batata de 2,3 ha?" "Quanto fertilizante líquido vou precisar para este trabalho?" Se você já se fez perguntas como essas, este mod ajudará a encontrar as respostas. 

- O número máximo de contratos e o valor gerado por ciclo são ajustados automaticamente ao número de campos do mapa.
 
- Você pode gerar novos contratos imediatamente através do botão "Novos contratos" ou excluir todos eles com o botão "Limpar contratos".

- Você pode classificar os contratos disponíveis por tipo e número de campo, por lucro total ou por lucro por minuto, para facilitar a localização do que você deseja.
 
- Você pode ativar mais de três contratos por vez.
 
- O mod adiciona novos combos de veículos para contratos, para o gerador de missão escolher.

- Com o botão "Detalhes" você pode ativar/desativar a exibição de informações adicionais do contrato. Como estimativas de custo para material de uso como fertilizante, herbicida ou sementes. Para contratos de colheita e enfardamento, mostra a quantidade mínima a ser entregue, e a quantidade que você pode manter (e vender). A partir disso, ele calcula o valor total do lucro para um contrato, ou seja, recompensa menos custo para contratos de fertilizar/pulverizar/semear e recompensa mais valor da colheita mantida para contratos de colheita/enfardamento. Ele ainda estima o tempo que você provavelmente precisará para a conclusão total do trabalho, levando em consideração a velocidade de trabalho e a largura de trabalho dos veículos/ferramentas de locação apropriados que são oferecidos no contrato.

Isenção de responsabilidade: Todos os valores mostrados na exibição de detalhes são ESTIMATIVAS. Você não deve tomá-los absolutamente, mas sim como uma indicação de quais contratos preferir entre outros.

Registro de alterações v1.2.5.0:
- modo difícil: contratos ativos expiram no meio da noite, penalidade por cancelamento
- modo de desconto: obtenha desconto no preço do campo, com base no número de missões
- menos avisos sobre veículos de missão desaparecidos

Registro de alterações v1.2.4.4:
- botões de filtro fixos para mostrar outros tipos de missão, se disponíveis
- exibição fixa de "tempo restante" para contratos de transporte no jogo MP
- contratos de ervas daninhas e fertilizantes agora também podem ser configurados para lazyNPC
- compatibilidade com outros mods de contrato

Registro de alterações v1.2.4.2:
- "NPCs preguiçosos" (deixe mais trabalho para contratos) pode ser configurado para ligar/desligar
- número máximo de contratos ativos configuráveis 
- indicador de contratos ativos com equipamentos emprestados
- botões de limpar / novos contratos em jogos MP funcionam apenas para o usuário mestre
- reconhecer FS22_DynamicMissionVehicles

Registro de alterações v1.2.4.0:
- Adicionado correção (interina) para "NPCs preguiçosos": deixe mais trabalho para contratos
- Permitir (futuros) outros tipos de contrato
- Corrigidos problemas de resolução de tela

Registro de alterações v1.2.3.0:
- Adicionado função de filtro de exibição para lista de contratos

Registro de alterações v1.2.2.0:
- Cálculo ajustado de manter/entregar valores para contratos de colheita/enfardamento
- Adicionado prevenção de conflitos com outros mods
- Adicionado suporte para FS22_SupplyTransportContracts, FS22_TransportMissions
]]>
		</br>
	</description>
	<iconFilename>icon.dds</iconFilename>
	<multiplayer supported="true" />
	<extraSourceFiles>
		<sourceFile filename="betterContracts.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/debug.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/events.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/gui.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/missionVehicles.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/options.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/settings.lua" />
		<sourceFile filename="scripts/userint.lua" />
	</extraSourceFiles>
	<l10n filenamePrefix="l10n/l10n" />
	<actions>
		<action name="MENU_EXTRA_3" category="SYSTEM" axisType="HALF" ignoreComboMask="true" />
		<action name="BC_MTOGGLE" category="SYSTEM" axisType="HALF" ignoreComboMask="true" />
	</actions>
	<inputBinding>
		<actionBinding action="MENU_EXTRA_3">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_d" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
		<actionBinding action="BC_MTOGGLE">
			<binding device="KB_MOUSE_DEFAULT" input="KEY_m" index="1" />
		</actionBinding>
	</inputBinding>
	<storeItems>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="missionVehicles/sw4014.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="missionVehicles/multipackD14.xml"/>
	</storeItems>
</modDesc>
